Kyle Johnson

Phone: 509-449-3698 / Email: kylejohnson.3525@gmail.com LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/kylesworkshopp

Portfolio: kymojo.github.io

Summary

Experienced in software design and project management. Familiar with object oriented programming and query languages. Confident and capable of learning new skills. Able to problem solve and think analytically. I care about organization and efficiency. I am dedicated to getting a job done well.

Skills

- Visual Studio .NET, C#, Java, MySQL, SQLite, Linux, C, 3D Studio Max, Adobe Creative Cloud, Game Maker Studio
- OO Programming and Design Patterns, GUI, Database, Algorithms, Digital Art and Design, Game Development

Experience

Career Services, EWU – Software Engineer / Team Lead

April 2015 - August 2015

I headed up a team that developed event registration software for use at career fairs. I learned a lot about the production process as well as how to work with a team and a client. The software is currently being used by Career Services at EWU.

 Responsibilities: Client relations, project planning, team organization, GUI development, database management

Eastern Washington University – Teacher Assistant / Project Grader

September 2013 – June 2015

I graded assignments for the 3D modeling and animation series. I also assisted with the 3D animation Mexican exchange program with CETYS students during the summer of 2014.

Education

Eastern Washington University – BS in Computer Science

Wenatchee Valley College – Associates of Arts and Sciences 2010-2012

References

Tom Capaul – Professor, EWU Computer Science Department

Phone: 509.359.7092 / Email: tcapaul@ewu.edu

Brian Kamp – Professor, EWU Computer Science Department

Phone: 509-359-4292 / Email: bkamp@ewu.edu

Shannon Turner – Career Advisor, EWU Career Services

Phone: 509-359-6417 / Email: sturner11@ewu.edu